A Guide to the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. records FA025
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2, 1875, 1878, 1916-2001 1969-2001; 2; 28 Cubic Feet
  - Grants, 1964, 1969-2001; 3
    - Health and Medical Program Grants, 1971, 1976-1998; 7
      - Medical Humanities Scholarships, 1987-1994; 2
        - Georgetown University Medical Center - Virginia A. Sharpe - Application, Part I, 1993 (Reel 48, Frame 671)
        - Georgetown University Medical Center - Virginia A. Sharpe - Application, Part II, 1993 (Reel 48, Frame 982)
        - Harvard University Medical School, 1992-1996 (Reel 49, Frame 1)
        - Harvard University Medical School - Allan M. Brandt - Application, 1992 (Reel 49, Frame 175)
        - History of Medicine Lecture Series, 1987-1990 (Reel 49, Frame 234)
        - Robert Wood Johnson Medical School / University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey, 1991 (Reel 49, Frame 269)
        - Robert Wood Johnson Medical School / University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey - Robert A. Aronowitz - Application, 1991 (Reel 49, Frame 318)
        - Scholars Committee, 1991-1993 (Reel 49, Frame 431)
        - Scholars Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Reel 49, Frame 477)
        - Scholarship Program Report, 1991 (Reel 49, Frame 627)
        - Scholarship Program Report, Part I, 1992 (Reel 49, Frame 718)
        - Scholarship Program Report, Part II, 1992 (Reel 49, Frame 846)
        - Scholarship Program Report - Ghiorse & Sorrenti, 1993 (Reel 49, Frame 923)
        - Scholarship Program Report, 1993 (Reel 49, Frame 992)
        - University of California, Los Angeles, Part I, 1991 (Reel 49, Frame 1015)
        - University of California, Los Angeles, Part II, 1991 (Reel 49, Frame 1127)
        - University of California, Los Angeles - Application, Part I, 1991 (Reel 50, Frame 1)
        - University of California, Los Angeles - Application, Part II, 1991 (Reel 50, Frame 205)
        - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill - Larry R. Churchill, PhD, 1991 (Reel 50, Frame 338)
        - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill - Larry R. Churchill, PhD - Grant, 1991 (Reel 50, Frame 399)
        - University of Pennsylvania - Russell C. Maulitz, Application, 1993 (Reel 50, Frame 501)
        - University of Pennsylvania - Russell C. Maulitz, Grant, 1993 (Reel 50, Frame 615)
        - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center at Dallas, 1993-1994 (Reel 50, Frame 666)
        - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center at Dallas - John Z. Sadler, Part I, 1993-1994 (Reel 50, Frame 823)
        - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center at Dallas - John Z. Sadler, Part II, 1993-1994 (Reel 50, Frame 1005)
      - Medical Research Grants, 1977-1996; 3
        The Foundation supported medical research in several areas, with particular emphasis, later, upon genetics, molecular pharmacology, bioengineering, and health services research.
        Series 3.7.3 is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
        - Series 3.7.3 - Grants - Health and Medical Program Grants - Medical Research Grants, 1977-1996 (Reel 51, Frame 1)
        - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, 1986-1992 (Reel 51, Frame 2)
        - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, 1993-1996 (Reel 51, Frame 148)
        - Hahnemann University, 1983-1985, 1991-1992 (Reel 51, Frame 251)
        - The New York Hospital and Cornell University Medical College, 1992-1995 (Reel 51, Frame 355)
        - New York Medical College, 1984-1992 (Reel 51, Frame 386)
        - New York Medical College, 1993-1994 (Reel 51, Frame 591)
        - New York Medical College, 1995-1996 (Reel 51, Frame 768)
        - Research Foundation of the State of New York for Kings County Hospital Center, 1990-1991 (Reel 51, Frame 1082)
        - Rockefeller University, 1986-1994 (Reel 52, Frame 1)
        - Salk Institute, 1977-1981 (Reel 52, Frame 192)
        - Salk Institute, 1983-1987 (Reel 52, Frame 355)
        - Salk Institute, 1988-1993 (Reel 52, Frame 480)
        - University of Minnesota, 1981-1985, 1993 (Reel 52, Frame 599)
        - University of Virginia, 1980-1982 (Reel 52, Frame 725)
        - University of Wisconsin Medical School, 1983-1987 (Reel 52, Frame 806)
        - The Whittier Institute for Diabetes and Endocrinology, 1990-1991 (Reel 52, Frame 863)
      - Medical Science Scholarships, 1980-1998; 4
        Grants in medical research were intended to address the need for greater involvement in research activities for younger physician scientists. The Culpeper Scholarships in Medical Science were offered for a term of three years through competitive application, to promote the research and progress of academic physicians. Annual applications were accepted for the four-year period 1987-1990, with one application allowed per institution. Up to three awards of $100,000 per year for up to three years could be awarded.
        An independent Scientific Advisory Committee, composed of seven physician scientists, selected the scholars. Charles E. Culpeper Scholars represented research activities in neuroscience, genetics, immunology, and molecular biology. Between 1988 and 1999, the Foundation provided research awards totaling $11 million to promote the activities of young physician scientists.
        The Visiting Professorships Awards were offered for a five-year period to individuals from an institution other than the applicant's affiliation. The Award was rotated annually among the departments of Medicine, Surgery, Pediatrics, Radiology/Radiotherapy, and Immunology/Genetics.
        Series 3.7.4 is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
        - Series 3.7.4 - Grants - Health and Medical Program Grants - Medical Science Scholarships, 1980-1998 (Reel 52, Frame 987)
        - Applicants, 1988 (Reel 52, Frame 988)
        - Applicants, 1989 (Reel 52, Frame 1101)
        - Applicants, 1990 (Reel 52, Frame 1147)
        - Applicants, 1991 (Reel 53, Frame 1)
        - Applicants, 1992 (Reel 53, Frame 102)
        - Applicants, 1993 (Reel 53, Frame 208)
        - Applicants, 1994 (Reel 53, Frame 344)
        - Applicants, 1995 (Reel 53, Frame 407)
        - Applicants, 1996 (Reel 53, Frame 463)
        - Applicants, 1997 (Reel 53, Frame 533)
        - Applicants, 1998 (Reel 53, Frame 696)
        - Baylor College of Medicine - Mark R. Hughes, MD, PhD, 1987-1992, 1995 (Reel 53, Frame 829)
        - Committed and Proposed Commitments for Fellowships, Visiting Professorships and Lectureships, 1990-1989 (Reel 53, Frame 931)
        - Correspondence, 1987, 1989-1997 (Reel 53, Frame 959)
        - Duke University Medical Center - Michael F. Seldin, MD, PhD, Part I, 1987-1991 (Reel 53, Frame 1017)
        - Duke University Medical Center - Michael F. Seldin, MD, PhD, Part II, 1987-1991 (Reel 53, Frame 1165)
        - Eligibility Requests, 1987-1990 (Reel 54, Frame 1)
        - The Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine and The Johns Hopkins Hospital - Mark S. Schlissel, MD, PhD, 1992-1996 (Reel 54, Frame 103)
        - Marketing Expenses, 1987-1988 (Reel 54, Frame 245)
        - Marketing and Press Releases, 1987-1988 (Reel 54, Frame 295)
        - Marketing and Press Releases, Part I, 1989 (Reel 54, Frame 324)
        - Marketing and Press Releases, Part II, 1989 (Reel 54, Frame 407)
        - Marketing and Press Releases, Part I, 1990 (Reel 54, Frame 554)
        - Marketing and Press Releases, Part II, 1990 (Reel 54, Frame 626)
        - Marketing and Press Releases, 1991 (Reel 54, Frame 710)
        - Marketing and Press Releases, 1992 (Reel 54, Frame 863)
        - Marketing and Press Releases, 1993 (Reel 54, Frame 964)
        - New York University Medical Center - Mary Ann Thompson Arildsen, MD, PhD, 1988-1991 (Reel 54, Frame 1047)
        - New York University Medical Center - Michael B. Whitlow, MD, PhD, 1990-1992 (Reel 54, Frame 1135)
        - New York University Medical Center - Michael B. Whitlow, MD, PhD, 1993-1994, 1996 (Reel 55, Frame 1)
        - Stanford University Medical Center - Russ B. Altman, MD, PhD, 1992-1993 (Reel 55, Frame 86)
        - Stanford University Medical Center - Russ B. Altman, MD, PhD, 1994-1996 (Reel 55, Frame 175)
        - Tufts University School of Medicine - Henry H. Banks, MD, PhD, 1989-1993 (Reel 55, Frame 336)
        - University of California - San Diego Medical Center - Fred Levine, MD, PhD - Grant, 1992-1995 (Reel 55, Frame 453)
        - University of California - San Diego Medical Center - Fred Levine, MD, PhD - Grant, 1996-1997 (Reel 55, Frame 622)
        - University of California, San Francisco - School of Medicine - William K. Hamilton, MD, PhD, 1989-1992 (Reel 55, Frame 815)
        - University of California, San Francisco - School of Medicine - Keith E. Mostov, MD, PhD, 1991-1996 (Reel 55, Frame 902)
        - University of California, San Francisco - School of Medicine - Edward L. Murphy, MD, PhD, 1988-1992, 1996 (Reel 55, Frame 1083)
        - University of Kansas School of Medicine - Barry T. Bloom, MD, 1987 (Reel 56, Frame 1)
        - University of Louisville - Visiting Professorship in Medical Sciences, 1985-1992 (Reel 56, Frame 58)
        - University of Michigan Medical Center - Joel D. Howell, MD, PhD, 1991-1993 (Reel 56, Frame 77)
        - University of Michigan Medical Center - Joel D. Howell, MD, PhD, 1994-1996 (Reel 56, Frame 198)
        - University of Minnesota Medical School - Karen Hsiao, MD, PhD, 1992-1993 (Reel 56, Frame 298)
        - University of Oklahoma - Visiting Professorship in Medical Science - Stanley Falkow, MD, 1983-1984, 1986, 1988, 1990 (Reel 56, Frame 343)
        - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center at Dallas - Sandra Lee Hoffman, MD, PhD, 1990-1996 (Reel 56, Frame 359)
        - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center at Dallas - Michael J. McPhaul, MD, PhD - Grant, 1987-1991, 1996 (Reel 56, Frame 512)
        - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - Ellen Wright Clayton, MD, PhD - Application, 1992 (Reel 56, Frame 604)
        - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - Ellen Wright Clayton, MD, PhD, 1993-1994 (Reel 56, Frame 821)
        - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - Ellen Wright Clayton, MD, PhD - Part I, 1995 (Reel 56, Frame 1009)
        - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - Ellen Wright Clayton, MD, PhD - Part II, 1995 (Reel 56, Frame 1128)
        - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - Katherine T. Murray, MD, PhD - Grant, 1988-1991 (Reel 57, Frame 1)
        - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - Katherine T. Murray, MD, PhD - Grant, 1992-1994 (Reel 57, Frame 206)
        - Washington University School of Medicine - Glen L. Hortin, MD, PhD, 1989-1994, 1996 (Reel 57, Frame 434)
        - Washington University School of Medicine - Daniel E. Goldberg, MD, PhD, 1991-1996 (Reel 57, Frame 600)
        - Yale University School of Medicine - Peter M. Glazer, MD, PhD - Grant, 1990-1992 (Reel 57, Frame 828)
        - Yale University School of Medicine - Peter M. Glazer, MD, PhD - Grant, 1993-1998 (Reel 57, Frame 950)
        - Yale University School of Medicine - Peter J. Hotez, MD, PhD, 1990-1992 (Reel 58, Frame 1)
        - Yale University School of Medicine - Peter J. Hotez, MD, PhD, 1993-1998 (Reel 58, Frame 231)
  - Historical Files, 1875-1995 1927-1952; 4
    This series of correspondence, personal business records, and ephemera concerns Daphne Seybolt Culpeper Sperl, the widow of Charles E. Culpeper, and her extended family members and friends. Daphne, who eventually became the chairman of the Coca-Cola Bottling Company of New York in her husband's place, was the daughter of a Pennsylvania farmer. She married Charles E. Culpeper in 1918 in Pennsylvania; a second marriage ceremony was held in New York in 1920. Both marriage certificates are included in this series.
    Personal letters include correspondence from some of Daphne's family and domestic staff who cared for her father in Pennsylvania. Some of the Seybolt and Sperl family relationships are described here. John and Susan Mornington were Daphne Seybolt's maternal grandparents. Elberta L. Seybolt Clauson was Daphne Seybolt's mother. George L. Clauson was Daphne Seybolt's step-father; George Claussen (b. June 22, 1861), alternate spelling 'Clauson,' was Elberta L. Seybolt's second husband. Hortense Rich served as caretaker to George Claussen, Daphne's step-father. Daphne Seybolt Culpeper married her second husband, George W. Sperl, and lived in the Wolfpit Road house in Connecticut. Augustus Sperl was possibly Daphne Seybolt (Culpeper) Sperl's father-in-law.
    Other unusual correspondence was written to Mrs. Culpeper from a friend of Jewish descent, Florence Wise, writing from France during World War II. Ms. Wise discussed the difficulties sustained operating a business in Europe at that time. The post-war fate of this individual however, is not further related.
    Although there is little information to be gleaned about the personal interests and temperament of either Charles or Daphne Culpeper in these records, Mr. and Mrs. Culpeper's interests of a humanitarian intent may be inferred from the newspaper article herein which notes the Culpepers' involvement in tracing the culprit in a fatal hit-and-run accident. While driving in upper Manhattan, the Culpepers pursued a "Corbalis Coupe forty-six blocks to one hundred and sixty-second street," where the alleged offender was arrested. This act of kindness resulted in a significant monetary award to the widow of the victim of the accident following court proceedings.
    Daphne Culpeper purchased property in Norwalk, Connecticut, in the mid-1940s after Mr. Culpeper's death. This cottage was to remain her home for the rest of her life. The grounds of this estate on either side of Silvermine Avenue included a red colonial structure and barn across the street, as well as a green barn and additional acreage to the west of the cottage. Known as the 'pink house' to her staff, it is rumored that Mrs. Culpeper did not live in this house for many years, and that during that time, the estate was used primarily for the purpose of entertaining and hosting weekend retreats. The home, including a wine cellar, was said to contain some unusual décor on the second floor of the building. Local tradesmen claim that Mrs. Culpeper spent her later years living alone in this house, allowing the formal landscape to deteriorate.
    Series 4 original materials have been retained. These materials have not been microfilmed.
    Series 4 is arranged in five subseries:
    Subseries 1 - The Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc.
    Subseries 2 - Archives History Project
    Subseries 3 - Charles E. Culpeper
    Subseries 4 - Daphne S. Culpeper Sperl
    Subseries 5 - Daphne S. Culpeper Sperl Family
    The Rockefeller Archive Center acquired this material in 2001 from the then owner of the 285 Silvermine Avenue property in Norwalk, Connecticut, the former home of Daphne S. Culpeper Sperl. The material included within this series was found in its entirety in the garage of the house. This documentation represents a separate accession received several years after the bulk of the collection was processed.
    - The Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc., 1939-1996; 1
      Series 4.1 includes corporate documents pertaining to the formation of the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. in 1939. The Corporate Structure binder dated from 1939-1993 and original corporate seals are included herein. Legal and financial documents include paperwork pertaining to both the Connecticut and New York offices. Capital relocation costs detail the closing of the Connecticut office in 1992.
      Additional historical information pertaining to the Culpeper Trust and Foundation is located in the document files within Accession 1, Series 3.
      - Corporate Documents, 1970-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Corporate Merger - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. and Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Cummings & Lockwood - Sections 1-8, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Corporate Merger - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. and Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Cummings & Lockwood - Sections 9-29, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Corporate Structure Binder, 1939-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Connecticut Corporation - Articles of Association, December 17, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Connecticut Corporation - Connecticut Amendment Limiting Corporation, December 31, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Connecticut Corporation - Corporate Claims Letter, January 11, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Connecticut Corporation - Federal Tax Exemption Letter, January 5, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Connecticut Corporation - Papers Related to Application for Federal Tax Exemption, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Connecticut Corporation - Stock Purchase Agreement between Estate and Foundation, July 2, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - New York Corporation - By-Laws Excerpt, Amended, June 26, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - New York Corporation - Certificate of Change of Purposes, November 20, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - New York Corporation - Certificate of Incorporation, November 18, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - New York Corporation - Certificate of Incorporation, Amended, November 26, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - New York Corporation - Certificate of Increase in Number of Directors, December 20, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - New York Corporation - Financial Statement, December 17, 1940-January 25, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - New York Corporation - Tax Exemption Request and Authorization Letters, November 25, 1955, December 2, 1955, March 16, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Appraisal and Inventory of Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. Office Interior, Stamford, Connecticut, 1989-1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Architectural Services - Pat M. Pulitano, PC, AIA, NCARB, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Computer Systems - Absolute Computer Systems, Inc., 1989-1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Computer Warranty and Registration, 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Foundation Relocation Budget, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - General Repairs - Elm Street Corporation, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Historical Documents Acquisition, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Local Area Network - Deloitte & Touche, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Miscellaneous Services, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Purchase of Office Furnishings and Decorative Arts - Bernadene Rand, Ltd., Interior Design, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Relocation Fixed Assets and Direct Expense Costs, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Relocation Services - Maris Corporation, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Relocation Services - Morse Corporation, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Office Capital Relocation Costs, Stamford, Connecticut - Southern New England Telephone Systems, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Corporate Seals - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Archives History Project, 1990-1995; 2
      The President of the Board of Trustees commissioned a history of the Culpeper Foundation to include the formation and evolution of the organization.
      - Archives and Foundation History Project, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Archives and Foundation History Project, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - Silver Tray, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 55)
        Sterling Silver Oval Tray with Inscription (18 1/2" wide X 12" high). Given to Charles E. Culpeper by his managers at Coca-Cola Company. Includes two Coca-Cola bottle images with detail.
        Inscription: "Chas. E. Culpeper with Christmas Greetings from Your Managers, 1937, Edward Laragy, Louis F. Betzigg, Alvin Culpeper, Walter Matthuus*, Frank K. Henderson, Louis Meyers, W. S. Lano, Haus* Ford Wilkinson, Gay P. Keith, A. F. Meyers, A. J. Ruddy, S. J. Bissett, Jjack V. Ursel*, Albert F. Bellingruth, Jr., Stwewart R. Cogswell*, W. N. Johnson, J. E. Washoughton*, Patrick J. Dempsey, A. E. Harpen, William Paltridge"
        *The spelling of certain names may vary from original inscription.
    - Charles E. Culpeper, 1916-1945, 1951; 3
      Business records pertaining to the Coca-Cola Bottling Company of New York, Inc. and the Root Glass Company, bottle suppliers and creators of the distinctive Coca-Cola bottle shape can be found in this subseries. Personal records include marriage certificates and license, dog ownership and pedigree information, and social security records.
      - Business - The Coca-Cola Bottling Company of New York, Inc., 1916, 1918, 1929-1937, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 34)
        Stock options, stock holdings and company assets.
      - Business - Root Glass Company, 1922, 1932-1933, 1936, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 35)
        Suppliers of Coca-Cola Bottles. Letters from Chapman J. Root.
      - Business - Silver Tray, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 36)
        "Christmas Greetings from Your Managers" Coca-Cola Company
        Located in Box 5.
      - Personal - Correspondence to Charles E. Culpeper and Daphne S. Culpeper, 1930, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Personal - Dog Pedigree and Related Materials, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
        'Gretta of Zorn' a.k.a. 'Peaches', 1942-1945 American Kennel Club Stud Book, Obedience Exercises Dog Pedigree Certificate, Gretta of Zorn (Pet Great Dane), 1942-1943 Letter, purchase of 'Peachers' from Laurado Kennels, Gretta of Zorn, 1942 Letters to and from breeder Larua Nadela
      - Personal - Last Will and Testament and Codicil of Charles E. Culpeper, July 24, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Personal - Marriage Certificates, 1918, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 40)
        Marriage License, Daphne Seybolt and Charles E. Culpeper, December 25, 1918, State of Connecticut Marriage License, Daphne Seybolt and Charles Emery Culpeper, State of New York, December 23, 1920
      - Personal - Personal Documents, 1917, 1936, 1939-1940, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 41)
        Notice of Enrollment Under Military Law, 1917 Letter, Federal Security Agency, Social Security entitlement
    - Daphne Seybolt Culpeper Sperl, 1927, 1937-1952; 4
      Materials in Series 4.4 include Daphne Culpeper's correspondence with family, a family caretaker to her father, and a friend in occupied France during World War II, as well as passbook savings books, home improvement estimates for the Norwalk property, and brochures collected during travel in Europe.
      - Correspondence to Daphne S. Culpeper Sperl, 1937, 1940-1945 (Box 3, Folder 42)
        Letters from step-father, George L. Clauson; Hortense Ritch, friend and caretaker of Daphne's father
      - Correspondence to Daphne S. Culpeper Sperl, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 43)
        Letters from step-father, George L. Clauson; Hortense Ritch, friend and caretaker to Daphne's father
      - Correspondence to Daphne S. Culpeper Sperl, 1947-1978 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence to Daphne S. Culpeper Sperl from Florence Wise, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Expenses and Savings Accounts, 1927, 1938-1942, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 46)